

# ALHIMNY DWINATA UTAMA SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- **2** +62-878-2535-1290
- alhimnydu.github.io/portofolio
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/alhimnydwinata-utama-490b9420a/

#### SUMMARY

Hello I am Alhimny, I have work experience as a software developer PHP, .NET (C#), NodeJS, and Python. I created some system for company engaged in digital solution, finance, and education. Software Development has been the best expression of my interest in invention and making my own career. I can contribute to the company by using an innovative and creative approach.

#### **RELEVANT SKILLS**

- Programming (Backend / FrontEnd)
  - PHP (CI / Laravel)
  - Python (Flask)
  - C# (.NET Framework / Core)
  - o Java
  - NodeJs
  - o React Native
  - AngularJs
- Database:

MySQL, Microsoft SQL Server, Firebase

- Additional
  - Deploy Website on Hosting
  - Understand GIT (Github / Gitlab)
  - AWS (EC2, ECS, Amazon S3, CodeBuild, CodePipeline, CodeDeploy)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**



PT Mitra Integrasi Informatika

On Site: BTN Syariah

Application Software Assoc Desember 2023 - Present

Skill: .NET, NodeJs, PHP, SQL Server, GIT,



Xtremax Teknologi Indonesia

Associate Software Development - Backend

January 2023 - October 2023

Skill: .NET, Sitefinity, AWS, GIT, BitBucket, Jira,

Confluence, SQL Server, Docker



Dana Pensiun Astra, Astra International
Information Technology Development & System
Analyst

January 2022 - Desember 2022

Skill: .NET, PHP, Codelgniter, MySQL, SSIS, Store

Procedure, SQL Server, GIT



Institut Teknologi Nasional (ITENAS)

Full-stack Developer (Internship)

March 2020 - November 2021

Skill: PHP, Codelgniter, MySQL, Deploy Hosting,

and GIT

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**



## **Bachelor of Computer Science**

Institution: Institut Teknologi Nasional

Bandung

Year of Graduation: 2021 Cum Laude, GPA 3.86

Scholarship

# **CERTIFICATIONS**



#### **Data Science**

Institution: Sanbercode

2021



## **Sertification Android Digital Talent**

Institution: Digital Talent & Dicoding

2019